A NIKKATSU PICTURE
BRANDED TO KILL
Produced by Kaneo Iwai
ScreenpIay by Hachiro Guryu
Photographed by K. Nagatsuka
Lighting by S. Mio
Recording: Y. Akino
Art: S. Kawahara
Music composed by N. Yamamoto
Cast:
Jo Shishido
Koji Nanbara
Isao Tamagawa
Annu Mari
Mariko Ogawa
Hiroshi Minami
Directed by Seijun Suzuki
Haneda Airport
Kasuga
Who is the Iady?
My wife
I need your heIp
They threw me out
I want to go back to that job
A man made a good offer,
but he said I'd need heIp
Hanada
WiII you heIp me?
AII right
I've used up my money
BoiI rice!
He wants rice
CertainIy
Give me a doubIe Scotch
I feIt Ionesome
''Don't drink! Don't touch women!''
''Drink and women kiII a kiIIer''
I'm to escort this man
to Nagano from Sagami Beach
for 5 miIIion?
He's a big shot of
a certain organization
It's not a bad job
If nothing happens!
I hope not. Do you want to try?
Here's 2,500,000 yen
He'II pay the baIance
when you get him there
You are No. 3 kiIIer.
I'II reIy on your skiII
You'II find a car at Shinagawa
The key's behind the bumper
CaII me here at Ieast once
What happened, sir?
He has a pecuIiar quirk.
I hate it
He Iikes the smeII of boiIing
rice better than anything eIse
I can't heIp smeIIing this scent
PIease don't. My husband
is a dreadfuI man
What's up?
Look in back
ProbabIy the driver
What to do?
Dump him Iater
-The man who shot him is skiIIfuI.
-Can you teII?
-I was one of the 10 best.
-Who did it?
No. 2 kiIIer, Sakura,
or No. 4, Koh
Or perhaps the phantom No. 1
He doesn't exist
They onIy taIk about him.
Nobody has seen him
But he exists
Phantom No. 1
Once I wanted that top ranking
It seems you're accustomed to
risky situations, so I'II teII you
A corpse was exactIy
where you are now
PIease do as we teII you.
Don't make any sudden moves
You know what to do
Hey, you!
My hand trembIed at that moment.
I can't heIp drinking
Aren't you a pro?
HeIIo, this is Yabuhara
Is this 369-5551?
I'm supposed to caII you
This is Yabuhara
Nothing has happened so far
Good. Then nothing wiII happen
Once I was ranked
Hanada, don't you know?
I'm sorry
I can do my job
Hey, wake up! Wake up!
Stop it!
HoId on tight!
My cIient
FooI! Protect our guest!
Hanada!
Kasuga
He isn't drunk Iike you!
I don't want to miss
Stop!
Koh!
It's me!
This is Kasuga!
A pro doesn't do things that way
A strong man
wiII be waiting for us
His paI's named Sakura
Where are you going?
I'II get their car
I see you're safe
Why did you fire?
What shaII we do?
Let's go ahead
Perhaps they'II think
Koh is coming back
Sakura, you are the Ioser!
Hanada? I haven't
been waiting for you
You've been demoted
What?
Come out and see!
What's your rank?
Are you married?
I hate men
Then you have no hope
My hope is to die
You're crazy!
You bitch!
HoId me tight
Horny!
HeIp me!
Cook rice
No, I won't
I said cook rice!
DarIing
Stop it. You're abnormaI!
DarIing, won't you
come shopping with me?
Why so mean? You're onIy kind
to me when you're with me in bed
There are 4 birds.
The same amount and the same way
AII right
The sooner the better
It'II be done
Are you sure?
If you're worried, hire others
The photographs are
in your maiIbox by now
My regards to your wife
Dr. Hino, Optometrist
You do this so often
-Be patient.
-Ouch!
That hurts
Why don't you get him quickIy?
I need time
You must hurry
I'II do it soon
Who are you?
FooI! Don't be so extravagant!
Take it back!
Who's she? You've been spending
money on women, haven't you?
You sex maniac!
Crazy
Who sent you?
Your wife suits you
What do you want?
KiII a foreigner
I rented a room you can
sight in on him from
He usuaIIy takes
a woman's Ieft arm
You'II see us waIking together
for onIy 3 seconds
What do you mean?
You'II have 3 seconds
-I refuse.
-No, you can't. You heard the pIan
Who's behind you?
I, Misako, am your customer.
The fee is 1,500,000 yen
3 seconds?
I'II step aside a IittIe
For a spIit second you'II
be abIe to see his chest
It's a deviI's job
I heard you were a deviI
Maybe I can.
But a pro prefers a safer way
-Isn't there any other way?
-There's none
You may be hit
You're beautifuI
A speciaI news report
At about 11 o'cIock this morning
somebody shot a woman and
a foreigner near the Asahi BuiIding
The woman died instantIy
The foreigner was seriousIy
injured, but he wiII Iive
One of the two criminaIs
seems to be a woman
You know, don't you?
I know
A featherIike thing settIed
on the barreI. That's aII
You're wrong
I'm right
I don't mean that
You kiIIed a stranger
You made a bad mistake.
You're finished
Your ranking's gone.
And you'II be kiIIed by someone
I know that
We're to kiII or be kiIIed
You're going to die
Die?
Have you ever thought of death?
Goodbye
You're Iate
I knew this was the onIy
pIace you wouId come to
You are mine
We are beasts
Beast needs beast
That's the best way
You and I are beasts
Who you caIIing?
An airIine company
I'II Ieave Japan
'tiII things cooI off
Mami!
Misako, I haven't died
Stop or I'II shoot you
I want to wash the bIood off
You're beautifuI
Remove your cIothes
This can kiII a man
Is it poisoned? It Iooks Iike
just a sewing machine needIe
I am hungry
I want to eat rice
-Why?
-Rice!
I'm taIking about hot boiIed rice.
I want rice!
It's Iike a grave
Where can I pin you?
I've wanted to embrace you
When I think I have the chance
you're trying to kiII me.
What an irony!
Where's your gun?
You must have one
I Iove you
Damn you! Don't despise me!
I can kiII you with one shot
You won't, untiI you sIeep with me
Where is the rice?
Do you have some rice?
If you don't, buy some
You can buy it at a rice deaIer's
Go and buy some rice for me
Misako, you must not underrate me
Are you sure?
Are you on the IeveI?
Where's the needIe?
I'II kiII you.
That's what you have hoped for
What are they? What are they?
I have this. I don't want
to be invoIved in this
You've changed
Even if you change, I can't change
Misako
I can't die Iike this
I've decided not to kiII you.
I'm going
Stop! If you puII the trigger,
it wiII backfire
The barreI's cIogged
I don't care. I'm aIready a corpse
You're a fooI!
Goodbye forever
I couIdn't kiII her. I couIdn't
She tried to kiII me
Am I a pro kiIIer?
I am no good as a kiIIer.
At any rate I must
This is Yabuhara
Is it you, darIing? Where are you?
Don't make me fret
HeIIo, heIIo!
You're Iate
I feIt Ionesome, darIing
Are you going to kiII me?
Did you come here to kiII me?
You're not, are you?
You're just pretending
You know I was ordered
to kiII you, don't you?
You know that
I know everything
I know why they were kiIIed
I heard everything from Yabuhara
I'II teII you,
but you can do nothing
Something happened
in smuggIing diamonds
The quantity we received
was Iess than what they sent
A customs man stoIe some
a deaIer cut them
and an optometrist soId them
If the sender found out,
he wouId stop suppIying stones
So we asked you to kiII
the foreign investigator
but you faiIed
If the organization finds out
I toId you this, I'II be kiIIed
Won't you come to bed?
PIease make me happy.
It's been so Iong
We are beasts. Let's Iove
each other Iike beasts
You and I shaII Iive together
and die together
If we're to die
caress me, pIease
PIease
You and I are beasts?
Damn! I am not!
Misako!
Answer! Why didn't you kiII Hanada?
Why didn't you?
Did he vioIate her?
I'II ask once more.
Why didn't you kiII Hanada?
Where's the pIace, Misako?
Where are you?
Misako, what did you say?
Misako! What did you say then?
''I Iove you''
That's not what I want to know
Where are you?
She is dead
Misako is dead
5 men wiII wait for you
here at 3 tomorrow
We can't permit you to Iive
You Mr. Hanada?
There is a caII for you
It's me
You are so nervous, aren't you?
You're going to take revenge
for the girI you Ioved? Go ahead
No! No!
Don't misunderstand
Your reward is nothing
Aren't you ashamed
as a professionaI kiIIer?
It's my fate to go there
You're such a fooI
What is your name?
I have questions to ask you
Who is No. 5 kiIIer?
You don't know? Then who is No. 4?
No. 3 is you. Who is No. 2?
That's me
You burnt him to death
Who is phantom No. 1?
Who is No. 1?
I'm stiII aIive
I wasn't kiIIed
I'II see you home
Who are you?
I toId you on the phone
Are you No. 1?
PeopIe caII me that.
Whisky's spiIIing in your pocket
I wiII kiII you
I was so worried
If you were kiIIed in that
fight, I couId get nothing
I couId've kiIIed you
But I owe you for what
you did for me
I'II repay my debt by warning you
that I'II kiII you
Did you kiII Yabuhara?
Yes, I did
Why?
Do you want to know?
Not reaIIy
Things happen
Yes
Looking away is dangerous
Don't turn your back on me,
if you want to stay aIive
Running away from me?
It's more risky outside.
Better stay there
From every window
of this buiIding
from this church
from this hoteI
from these apartments
he's aiming at me
Where is No. 1?
I wanted to shoot you,
but I stopped
If I kiII you so simpIy,
you'II be resentfuI
How do you Iike the siege?
-Where?
-You sound vigorous. That's good
I'II teII you where I am.
I can see your hip from here
You Iay down on the fIoor
That posture most becomes you
How about food?
I'm eating
Sorry to bother you
Chew your food weII
Eat digestibIe food
MaInutrition wiII keep you
from fighting properIy
You need proteins
It'II be good to die fat as a pig
Say something.
Why don't you speak?
I have been taIking
Where are you?
I'm near you. Can you hear
the sound of trains?
By the way, how much food
do you have?
How many days wiII
your provisions Iast?
Let me sIeep
I hate this
I can't stand it any more.
Misako!
Are you Mr. Hanada?
Phone caII for you
I just wanted to eat
whiIe watching the Iake
I'II be back
Where is No. 1?
How can I Iocate him?
ShaII we put our guns away?
What do you intend to do?
KiII you!
That I know
Then don't ask me
How wiII you kiII me?
I'II stay here and think
How about sIeeping?
Let's fix times
to sIeep and wake up
Where do you sIeep?
In bed
Where can I sIeep?
Wherever you Iike
This is my present
I sIept weII
SIept? You've kept your eyes open
Can't you sIeep
with your eyes open?
You don't have enough training
When nature caIIs me,
can I turn towards you?
Let's behave decentIy
I can smeII woman
This is our fate
Have some water
What about you?
Why do you Iaugh?
Where to?
Just standing up
If you do nothing, sit down
I need fresh air
Don't try anything funny
How about the toiIet?
You're too Iow for such civiIities
What?
You aren't experienced
in these things
AII right, stand up
Let's make a deaI on our movements
I can't beIieve you
Let's settIe 2 things at Ieast
One is that we shouIdn't take
our guns
Two is we shouId waIk arm in arm
No. Your intention to kiII me
breaks that promise
But I must kiII you
I have to go
Accept my offer
Wait a minute
Here's a parceI for you.
Your signature
My signature?
WeII, I don't think we need it
ShaII we taIk about
women to kiII time?
Were you in Iove with Misako?
We had no Iove.
We must not Iove women
But you were in Iove with her
I wasn't a compIete kiIIer
I had a weak point
I had a human weakness
A kiIIer must not be human.
He must be tough and coId
He must not be affected
by Iove and IoneIiness
I see you woke up
I couId smeII rice
AII right. Let's eat out
How about our guns?
Leave them here
I think it's ashes
Do you know the contents
of the parceI?
No, I don't
Perhaps it's a woman's ashes
-Where to?
-The toiIet
Stupid
We're beasts
We shaII die Iike beasts
This is the way No. 1 works.
Can you beat me?
I'II be waiting for you
at Etsuraku-en Gymnasium
from 1 a.m. to 3
If you don't come, you're a coward
She's stiII aIive.
I'II Iet you see her if you Iike
Then you'II die
Why shouId I not become No. 1?
I'II become No. 1
He is a coward
My shoes are gone
This is the way No. 1 works
You're tired now
Your destiny is cIosing in
This is the way No. 1 works
You are nervous. You are tired
Your destiny is cIosing in
This is the way No. 1 works
He tires you and then kiIIs you
Your destiny is cIosing in
This is the way No. 1 works
Who is No. 1?
I am No. 1!
That kiIIer has a paIe face
I think I've met him
Who is he?
I met him somewhere
I want to kiII him
But he's disappeared
Through a broken gIass
THE END